<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello Friend</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>C. Eisenstein - Sacred Economies Intro</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/09/c.-eisenstein-sacred-economies-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/09/c.-eisenstein-sacred-economies-intro/</guid>
      <description>Sacred Economics traces the history of money from ancient gift economies to modern capitalism, revealing how the money system has contributed to alienation, competition, and scarcity, destroyed community, and necessitated endless growth. Today, these trends have reached their extreme—but in the wake of their collapse, we may find great opportunity to transition to a more connected, ecological, and sustainable way of being.
This book is about how the money system will have to change—and is already changing—to embody this transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The economic science</title>
      <link>/economics/the-economic-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/economics/the-economic-science/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to setup your computer for privacy</title>
      <link>/howtos/how-to-setup-your-computer-for-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/howtos/how-to-setup-your-computer-for-privacy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Grin &amp; Mimblewimble</title>
      <link>/grin/introduction-to-grin-mimblewimble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/grin/introduction-to-grin-mimblewimble/</guid>
      <description>19 july 2016 Tom Elvis Jedusor released in the mailing list a file containing a new cryptographic feature useful for the blockchain. Omomorphic crypyography
 Three months lates Andrew Polestra built the white paper.
 It forms the first organization: Andrew which is gone, Ignotus peverell, the core team and the community
 The 15 of january, two years later, the first implementation of Mimblewimble is released, it’s called Grin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library</title>
      <link>/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/</guid>
      <description>Here you can find the pivotal points for economics and cryptocurrencies, through the eyes of the big thinkers that shaped a lot of minds. All the content on the other sections points to these resources, that is, what is written takes inspiration from the books and documents you can find below.
This page is divided in two parts. The first one is a selected path to understand as fast as possible what we are talking about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an economic researcher with a master degree in economic science. Since the beginning of my journey I’ve always wondered what is that strange thing we call money.
Money has always intrigued me because, if you think about it, it’s what unify us and divide us at the same time. We all wake up to earn money for a living and we all use money to exchange things and properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prova</title>
      <link>/post/prova/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/prova/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>